Good afternoon.
>> Yes, sir.
>> Okay. John Kim from ESPN. Um, you've had
a journey along the way here. How did
you prepare as you're going along the
way as you advanced in your career to
put yourself in this kind of a spot? Uh
just been around some of the talented
coaches, great minds that I've been a
part of uh growing up, you know, from
Marvin Lewis to Vance Joseph, Mike
Zimmer, Luan Romo, uh and even as
recently as Kevin Okonnell and Brian
Flores, uh they've prepared me and being
around them, learned lessons, how to
lead, how to structure their side of the
ball, um how to implement certain
learning techniques and uh finding out
about the culture amongst the guys have
helped guide me to where I am today.
>> You've you mentioned the names that
you've coasted with. How do they shape
your defensive philosophy and what what
is it that you want to bring here?
>> Versatility, uh adaptability,
um using our players strengths to the
best of their ability,
maximizing what they do, being a feature
that and then minimizing the things that
they don't do well. And each coach has
provided a certain way of highlighting
whoever that athlete may be and whatever
that strength may be that allow them to
get to their highest level. And so my
ability and learning from those guys in
terms of how to tap into each individual
player and each individual player is
different. Um, but it all starts with
the relationships. And the biggest thing
that I've gotten is in this profession
is how to attack and relate to players
um, and connect with those guys. And
that starts with the relationships
aspect of it. And what does that mean?
That starts with trust.
>> Hi, Nikki. Jeffala with the athletic.
Um, as you've worked with different
coordinators, different players, are
there things you've kind of picked up
along the way where you're like, if I if
I ever get my shot at calling a defense,
this is what I want to do. I want to do
this differently. I want to keep this.
Have there been any like small things
that you're like, if I get my chance, I
I want to implement this.
>> Sure. You naturally want to be uh
multiple uh because I've been around so
many different schemes. I think that's
that's an advantage of mine. uh there
aren't too many schemes that I have not
been a part of. There's, you know,
everyone comes from some type of tree.
And so because of that, I've been able
to uh to answer your question, be able
to implement various things from each
scheme that I like and I want to pull
from. So whether it's the Zimmer scheme,
hey, I like this on third down. I like
the mug looks there, or if it's Flores
and the versatility and how we can use
uh one person in multiple ways based off
of their strengths. Uh that's what you
want to pull from.
>> And how much did your your year at LSU
kind of shape you in particular?
>> It was great lessons at LSU. Uh having
the ability to lead a staff uh I think
the defensive staff at that time was 16
on defense alone. Um and so that's a
large staff that you have to organize um
and and be structured in a way that
you're very efficient in how you meet
and how you prepare dayto day and how
you get the players prepared. Um, and so
with that also with 16 different
personalities and you're dealing with
grown men and everyone's different and
everyone has different backgrounds,
different experiences that they can
bring, you wanted to make it a
collaborative effort, right? And and
include everyone. And you want guys that
can contribute, guys that have high
character, guys that are also teachers
and they can communicate in their own
light. And so being at LSU, learning how
to deal with different personalities,
not only from the player perspective
because that's been, you know, you get
used to that at various levels, but in
terms of at that level in the SEC and
going into SEC competition and what that
means, uh, was very instrumental for me.
>> Yes.
>> Hey, Coach David Aldridge with the
Athletic. Welcome back.
>> Thank you. Appreciate you.
>> Um, you you have all kinds of you
mentioned different experiences. I just
wonder if you have a sense of 34 or 4-3
just at the jump just off the outset for
this group.
>> Uh multiple I think 3 43 they're just
numbers still seven man spacing.
So I always say it's not how they line
up is how they wind up and so you can
create that number system in numerous
ways.
>> With regards specifically to Frankie
Louvu they used him in different ways
the fir each of the first two seasons. I
wonder what you think his best
utilization of his talent and skill set
would be.
>> Love Frankie Lou. We watched him on
tape. He's a guy that uh before I even
got here that we would watch and put on
the tape in our meeting room. I love his
athleticism. Uh he's best going
downhill. Uh getting them matched up on
running backs. That's always a key.
You're going to hear that a lot in terms
of matchability and and putting guys in
advantage positions. He's best when he
can when he can go down. He'll use his
athleticism, win on edges, uh use his
speed, uh so time, distance, and space
to encounter those matchups. And you
want to put him in that situation where
he's matched up on a running back. And I
think running backs are one of the guys,
uh on offense that gets the least amount
of reps and protections.
>> Hey, Coach Liam Griffin with the
Washington Times. Uh Coach Gwyn had
talked about how things change over the
last 5 to 10 years. A defense that was
effective 10 years ago, maybe not be as
effective now. What have you seen change
in defensive trends across the league
since you got to the NFL about 10 years
ago?
>> Uh the coverages, it's almost like uh
things come back full circle. So uh at
that time years ago, people were leaving
the spot drop schematics and they were
going more match coverages. So match
three quarters and things of that
nature. And now you're starting to see a
trend coming back full circle to where
schemes are starting to become more
vision based. Um and especially on early
down. So you see that trend starting to
happen. Uh you see guys going more shell
coverage where at one point it was
really middlefield closed just in terms
of structurally. Um and so there's
always things that you can pull from 10
years ago that is still prevalent to
today in terms of the physicality and
the fundamentals and the techniques that
will never change no matter what year
that is. Uh so you want to emphasize
that and lean on that and I think that's
where defenses can continue to grow. If
you watch the last couple of years of
the Super Bowl, it's come down to
fundamentals and techniques uh and
winning the line of scrimmage. So, that
will never change in my in my opinion.
>> And why was Washington the right fit?
What was it about this coaching staff or
this building or this locker room, these
players that appealed to you?
>> Well, that's a loaded question. I mean,
it's uh again, I grew up in the area. I
grew up, you know, wearing the burgundy
and and uh supporting the Washington
organization. I I went to elementary
school, middle school, literally right
across the street from where the stadium
is in Palmer Park, Maryland. I went to
Kimmore Middle School and I went to
Matthew Henson Elementary. So, uh,
growing up a diehard fan, uh, the
family's backing it. So, when the
opportunity came, I thought it was a,
uh, a win-win situation, I want to put
my best foot forward. And then when you
talk about the people in the building
such as Dan Quinn, such as Adam Peters,
uh, great ownership with Josh Harris and
the crew. Um, one I want to say thank
you for that. By the way, I didn't mean
to say I want to start off just by
thanking the ownership Josh Harris,
thanking Dan Quinn, thanking Adam Peters
for the opportunity uh that they've
afforded me. But when you're around
certain people and you see the alignment
of the organization, ownership,
management, head coach, quarterback, uh
it's a win-win for not only the DMV, but
a win-win for me as well.
>> Thank you.
>> Coach John Durant with W USA. You
mentioned uh wanting to maximize all
your players and and be versatile. You
mentioned Frankie Luvu as well. any
other guys that you've watched that you
can't wait to to get on the the field
with here?
>> Yeah, I mean, I had a chance to speak
with quite a few players already and uh
they're all excited to get going just as
I am. But I think the team is filled
with some versatility players. Um, and I
think you can be they can be used in
several ways. You look at a a sr still
who was very versatile coming out of
college and the things that he was able
to accomplish at University of Michigan,
not only winning the championship, but
the way he done it, right, and how he
led those guys there, when you talk to
the guys from that championship team,
everyone points to him as being the
leader. You look at Aquan Martin who I
know evaluating coming out, you know, we
were like, "Hey, is he a safety? Is he a
nickel? Is he a corner?" Uh that's
another guy that has versatility, you
know, and then I think when you look at
Will Harris and how he's able to move in
the line of scrimmage, cover tight ends
on the deep halves. Uh you look at a
Jordan McGee, another guy who's on the
ball, off the ball, the list goes on and
on. You look at a, you know, Javon
Kinlaw who can play all different levels
up front. And so the talent is there,
the skill set is there. It's our job
with the staff to maximize those skill
talent. And I'm excited to work with the
staff that we have. uh there's going to
be a lot of collaborative effort going
forward and uh the communication and we
get a chance to teach right you know
talk about the foundation from ground up
and uh
trying to connect to these players and
find out how they learn and I think
that's the biggest thing going forward
uh to be able to utilize the versatility
you got to figure out how do they learn
uh we all as human beings we learn
differently right and so each player is
going to fall into one of the four
categories of learning styles and it's
our responsibility to figure out if
visual auditori auditory uh read and
write or if it's kinesesthetic learners
and that's our job to pull that out of
them.
>> Yeah.
>> Uh good afternoon coach David Harrison
WSA9. Uh welcome home.
>> Thank you. Appreciate you.
>> I uh got more than a few questions I
could ask you. Let's let's start here.
Um how much obviously you've done a lot
of homework and you've talked to some
guys like you mentioned. How much do you
want to have much I should say this. How
much of the plan for each individual guy
do you want to have in place before you
meet them? And then how much obviously
is going to be uh dictated by getting to
know them further?
>> Uh I think it's a balance, you know. So
coming in already, I've had a chance to
watch the tape on uh just about everyone
here in the building on the team. I've
developed an here's a teaching
background. I've developed an an IEP for
each player, an individualized education
program, but just for football, uh in a
way that these are the things that I see
on tape that they do well, things they
can improve in. how can we as a staff
assist them in that improvement? And
then when you meet that player and that
player comes here and you start to get
to know that guy, you may have to tweak
it a little bit in terms of again their
learning style. All right? Is it more of
walkth through? Is it more film based?
Is it more auditory? So then we can
tweak it, but at least the overall uh
30,000 foot view plan of how to improve
that individual player has already been
assessed. And as you go through these
players, obviously you've got one year,
two year, even sometimes more of NFL
tape on these guys, but sometimes what
they were able to do in college is
different than what they've been asked
to do in the NFL. Will you go back to
that on your own and maybe try to look
at some of those things that you can
reintroduce to their skill set in the
NFL or do you kind of let them maybe
tell you, hey, these are some things
I've done before that I haven't been
able to do here that I would like to do
moving forward?
>> Well, a little bit of both. Um, you
know, every player, every player sees
themselves differently than we as
coaches and you as media may see them,
right? And so, as rightfully so. Um, but
that getting to know that player first
starts with I want to go back to me
finding out what's their why,
how they're motivated, is it external
motivation or internal motivations. That
opens the lines of effective
communication. And then when those lines
of effective communications are open,
then now we can kind of tap into what
you can and cannot do based off of your
strengths and then have an open dialogue
of this is what I see that you do well.
These are things I these are areas I
think you can improve in. How do you see
that? And then come to a a kind of an
agreement and then move forward from
that point on. But I think it's
definitely a it's a constant open lines
of communication. You got to have
communication. You know, you don't want
any void. You know, negativity kind of
fills the void when it's empty, right?
So, we want to continue to have that
effective line of communication, both
player and coach, and that way we can
help them grow as individuals.
But you got to know the person before
you know the player.
>> Yeah.
>> Coach, good afternoon. Chad Ricardo with
Fox 5. With all of your resume and with
all of your experience that you bring
here to the table, what is the biggest
thing about you yourself that's going to
allow for you to impact not only this
defense, but this organization?
>> Relationships. Uh, I think one of my
strengths are has is the ability to
connect to people. Um, I've taught at
every different level. I've coached at
every different level from division one,
division 2, division three, one doubleA,
high school. I've taught high school,
coached in the CFL, and now in the NFL.
And what you come to find out is when
you've been in so many different levels,
you come across so many different
people, right? And they come from all
different backgrounds of life. And you
got to find a way to meet them where
they are.
that connection allows the relationship
to grow that it can allow the growth of
that person to get to the highest levels
and they can maximize their abilities.
And so, um, I intend to get to know
these players, uh, as I've already done
so far on a personal level, you know,
you know, talk about their wives and
their kids and so forth. Um, but that's
my strength is the ability to connect
and build relationships and to teach.
Um, and then everything else shows up on
the tape.
>> Dante Scott Abraham, ABC7, welcome back
home.
>> Thank you. I appreciate it.
>> I'm sure it's very exciting. Um, fans
love buzzwords, right? So, they they
they probably want to know,
>> what will a Washington le defense by
Dante Jones look like and feel like?
>> Buzzwords. Uh, I'm not going to say, you
know, all the typical coaching
buzzwords, but I will say that, uh, when
you turn on the tape, you joy would be
one. All right, that would be the number
one thing that if you turn on the tape
or you watching TV from wherever you may
be watching from, to see the joy that
these players have when they step on the
field, the joy that they have when they
playing with one another, the
camaraderie, um, that's the number one
thing uh, that we want to have on the
defense. Uh, I think when you have when
you see joy out there, guys are playing
selflessness and you're seeing a team
defense and you're seeing guys who they
don't care who makes the play long as
someone makes the play and they're
willing to um take on a double team or
take this pick so that you can kind of
clear up and they're going to learn that
the word sacrifice although has a
negative connotation will be seen in a
different light meaning it's not what am
I willing to give up it's what I'm what
I'm willing to do for and having that
mindset um amongst the whole team will
provide that joy. Uh but outside of the
joy, you want to see, you know, guys
that are, uh, you know, constantly
attacking the football, um, creating
takeaways. You want to see guys playing
with some type of I some high IQ, some
type of intelligence out there, uh, and
communicating. So, uh, but the joy is
the number one thing that you want to
see. I'm not going to use any other
buzzwords that, you know, trigger
things, but joy would be the collective
unit.
>> You said something earlier that stood
out to me. You said it starts with
trust. Yes.
>> So, how do you earn the trust of your
players with them buying in to what
you're coaching?
>> Well, for them to buy into what I'm
coaching, they have to one buy into who
I am as a person. Uh, and that I
genuinely have their best interest at
heart. And how do they do that is for me
getting to know the person and not the
player. Uh, that's me getting to know
again their upbringing, how they get to
where how they got to where they are.
Uh, the people that matter to them in
life. Uh, that's me asking them about,
hey, how's your mom or how's your loved
one? How's your child? How did they do
in that basketball game? And you start
to develop that relationship. And when
you develop that relationship, they
realize that, you know what, he he he
cares more than just if I make this play
or not. He's really invested in me. And
so, because he's invested in me, I can
now become invested in him and what he's
teaching and buying in. Because when
you're dealing with especially football
players or just any athlete or people in
general, for me to listen to you, I have
to be invested in you, right? If there's
no connection there with that, how hard
is it is how willing am I to
be where I need to be and do what I have
to do if I'm if I don't feel like you
really have my best interest at heart.
And so, uh, just starting, I think
that's what the offseason's about. It's
a great opportunity to, you know, them
to get to know me, me, get to know them.
And uh and I think being around Coach
Quinn, you can get a sense of that that
he's a people's person. He's about
relationships, the players that he's
brought in this in this building and the
culture that he has. Uh I'm just I'm
just reliving I'm just going through and
fulfilling the vision that he's already
set forth. That's all I'm just moving to
continue to move the needle that way. Uh
because he's already had the foundation
of that in this building and just the
guys that I've met and just watching him
interact with people.
>> Yeah. Hey Dante, congrats on the new job
and welcome back to DC. JP Finley with
NBC4. Um, you've talked about wanting to
be multiple and all your different stops
in your coaching journey, but the last
stop in Minnesota was with an
ultraaggressive scheme in in Brian
Flores. How much of that do you want to
bring to Washington?
>> Well, it's about what we do well uh if
we have the players uh and their skill
sets. Some of the skill sets are to be
aggressive by nature. I'm an aggressive
person by nature just in in the
background and not only with Brian
Flores, his his aggressiveness looks a
little bit different than what it may
have been in the past. But really, if
you think about it, there's not much
there aren't many differences between
him and Mike Zimmer in terms of the
aggression. There's just, you know, Zim
was more third down aggression. With
Flo, it's more first, second, and third
down aggression, right? Uh and it just
looks differently. you know, Zim is more
mug looks, whereas, uh, Flo is more all
offsets, but there will be some
incorporation of all that. Um, I don't
want to get too much in the X's and O's,
but, uh, we will try to dictate the
terms and change the math. There's a
buzz word for you. Um, but we will use
that just with our adaptability and
versatile approach, but I think the way
the players help shape that. So, it's
all about players first and scheme
second. And so, based off what our
players can do, we will do. Um if
players can't do that then we will do
and put them in situations where they
can be at their best and so yes by
nature I'm an aggressive person uh by
nature we want to become more aggressive
in some way shape or form is that
pressures or is that just being more of
attacking is that being more uh
technique and fundamentals attacking
blocks defeating blocks tackling and
just doing the routine things routinely
that could also be seen as being
aggressive as well when you're just
playing technique and so it's based off
what we have player-wise
>> and And Dan Quinn mentioned that before
you guys started talking about the
roster, he asked you to just watch
everything. Yes.
>> When you watch this defense from last
year, what would you describe as the
strengths?
>> Young and athletic. I would say young
and athletic. I know there's uh there
are some uh there are some older pieces
there, but for the most part, especially
the guys that are we know we have in our
system here. You look at the back end
with we're talking about Sam Steel, Trey
Amos, Quan Martin, Will Harris, you
know, those guys are athletic. And you
throw in a Reeves in there as well who
provides some versatility, you know, and
and Owens also another guy who's
versatile. You look at McGee, you look
at Luvu, uh you look at Madrono, those
guys are athletic and they're young, you
know, and up front you have some savvy
bats up there. And then you have Newton
who's also a young player who has some
mobility inside in the interior D line.
And so when you look at that, the first
thing that jumps off the tape is these
guys can run and hit. Um, and so you
definitely want to use that to where
guys are going forward versus going
backwards.
>> Yeah.
>> Hey Dante, Mitch Tishler with Money
Metal Sports. Um, as you've looked at
kind of the defense from last year and
the players that are coming back over,
have you started talking with Adam
Peters, Dan Quinn about the types of
players that you want to bring in, I
guess. What are some of those
characteristics that you look for?
>> Uh, one, tough, uh, physical, uh,
versatility. We talked about that. Um,
and just with anything, our ability as a
staff, our players ability to be
adaptable and whatever that may looks
like. Uh, because when you're coming in
and you may have a different vision on a
certain player, um, or you view
versatility more than someone who, you
know, is a first and second down Mike
linebacker, just all parties being
versatile and being adaptable in that.
Um, and I think being on the same page
and I I have a great feel and sense that
even in the hiring process when we're
talking about position profiles that
their vision the vision that we have as
a collective unit and the vision that
we're having as a staff uh is is is on
board with the same thing. So we're
we're we're aligned that way.
>> Yeah.
>> Hey Dante, uh Ben Standigo with the last
man standing in the team 980. Um I when
you go in for an interview typically you
highlight some of your some of the your
stronger points. What was it like when
you had a conversation about 31 to
nothing?
>> We didn't discuss the uh 31 to nothing.
Um yeah, we didn't we didn't talk about
that, but I will say it was just about,
you know, um it's it's just again it's
about the joy about the game, you know,
any given Sunday. Uh that was a very
tough team to prepare for you know with
again you know with Terry coming back
that game you had Jaden Daniels uh you
know provide a lot of issues or it's a
lot of issues that that the offense can
provide and I'm looking forward to being
a part of it this year and uh you know
me and David we have some history
together when we're at Minnesota at the
same time together and so it'll be fun.
It'll be fun to kind of just merge all
this together and so that we can also
have a uh successful year in 2026.
>> And you mentioned some of the youth on
this team also you had older guys like
Bobby Wagner and Von Miller who who are
free agents. Um
how do you kind of envision like
obviously I think in general this team's
got to get younger. So how do you view
from your perspective of hey we need
some experienced guys but we also have
to have more athleticism, speed, things
like that.
>> I think it's you have to have a little
bit of both. I I I think you can't go
too far on either end of the spectrum.
So, you know, you have to have some
veterans to kind of balance those things
out and help those guys come along
because those veterans can provide
knowledge
various ways, right? It's not just on
the field, it could be off the field, it
could be how do I study, how do I watch
film, how do I become a pro. And so
having veterans around uh I think is a
great piece and the great thing is it's
all speeds up the development of young
players.
>> Yeah.
>> Hey there, Coach Jones. My name is Candy
Wall. I'm from Buoie TV.
>> Hi.
>> Um so welcome back.
>> Thank you. Appreciate you.
>> So um kind of uh pulling on the thread
of Nikki's question. Um as a H.B.CU
graduate and having coached on the
H.B.CU level, how has that shaped who
you are today?
It's the foundation of who I am today.
Uh having to attend and graduate from
Oregon State University. Um and then
becoming getting my first coordinator
experience at Buoie State University. Uh
so as you can see the foundation of who
I am and why relationships are so
important to me is because those players
that I that you come in come in contact
with either coaching or playing with uh
it's it's special and there's a bond
that's there. Um, and so
coming to Morgan State, it's, you know,
it's it's not about the glitz and the
glamour in terms of, uh, what some PWIS
may be about, but you find a family
atmosphere. Um, you know, I I learned
that, uh, you know, you miss a class,
that coach is going to going to be on
you like, why you miss this class? And,
you know, that means something and that
helped build who I am today as a car in
my character because now I understand
that, you know what, he cared. those
coaches that that coached me at Morg at
Morgan State, you know, they cared for
me and they cared about my development,
not just as a football player, but as a
person, as a man, as a father, as a
husband, they cared about that
development. And I think that's what the
H.B.CU do. Uh they help bridge that gap.
They help provide
the experiences of yes, you're not alone
as you continue to grow and as you
continue your journey uh post high
school. Um and you learn a lot of
different things going through those
processes.
>> And when you take a look at how the NFL
continues to evolve um from the
offensive perspective, what makes these
NFL offenses so hard to defend the top
uh offenses?
Well, it's their it's their blend, first
of all, the quarterback play, right? The
quarterback is a quarterback driven
league. Uh, and what you're starting to
see is the blend from, let's say,
college football coming into the NFL,
and it has been for a while. You're
seeing less under center two back
downhill runs. You're seeing more spread
open shotgun. Uh, you're seeing the
influence, the QB run game. You're
seeing that influence from college
football. And what's happening is
unfortunately there's some of the a
there's a large population of coaches uh
in the NFL that hasn't been in college
football in years, right? And the game
is changing a little bit. And so now
you're starting to visit in clinic with
college coaches and say, "Hey, how do
you stop this? How have you guys what
have you guys done with this particular
scheme?" And you see the crossover uh
between NFL and college that the game is
becoming more dynamic. Everyone wants
the points on the board. They're
spreading it out. Uh
defensively, we like to try to take
advantage of the open and spread looks.
Uh hence the aggressiveness over there
that he talked about earlier. Um but
that's where the game is changing. It's
it's more passing. It's a passing
league. Um you know, it was good to kind
of see the a running back get the MVP in
the Super Bowl. You know, that's kind of
been unheard of lately. Um, you know,
it's been more quarterback driven and
more ball in the air type of offenses.
>> Yes.
>> Hi, coach. Uh, welcome back to the DMV
home again. Uh, Donna Hopkins Pro
Football Plus. Uh, we can always learn
new things about ourselves with all of
your experiences that you've had, you
know, in coaching. What have you learned
most about yourself as you embark on
this new opportunity?
>> Uh, perseverance.
Um the journey wasn't a a typical
journey. Uh at 47 years old, this is my
26th year coaching, 16 in college. Um in
my 10th year in the league, but uh
perseverance, you know, not giving up,
continue to move forward, push forward,
be resilient, um
face adversity and success in the same
light, I would say. Um you know, it's uh
it's different. You think back to
you know, when I was 26 years old or
really
23 years old, um, you know, sleeping in
the car at 23 is different than sleeping
in the car at 33, which I experienced
both of those to try to strive to be
where I am today. So, perseverance and
then, uh, trusting in God.
>> With your defensive staff, what is the
message that you want to deliver to them
as you all bond together as a unit? Uh
definitely um talked about being a
collaborative having a collaborative
input. I don't we don't care where good
ideas come from. Um you know meeting the
staff you can feel it already the juice
to feeling the strong dynamics to be
able to have some creativity in the
room, some some uh dialogue in the room.
Definitely have to have that open lines
of communication. But you get a sense of
there there's a there's a lack of ego in
the room which is great. uh you can see
that we have a staff of guys that are
can be at their best in the darkest of
moments. Uh what you look for, but you
also you're seeing teachers and you're
seeing communicators, you're seeing uh a
certain sense of humility in there and
you see their character really come to
light. And I think with all that um
that's a great environment where things
can grow and uh we can bring this all
and we can make it all come to life in
terms of our vision that we have amongst
the defense and for the organization as
a whole under coach Quinn.
>> Coach, welcome back home
44 and NBC4 here in DC. Uh
congratulations on this opportunity. Can
you talk about what your family has told
you now that you're back? And also, you
touched on the fact that you slept in
your car. Can you elaborate what that
experience was like for you and what
made you just keep going even after all
of that?
>> Uh, so for the family, um, all my family
is still here. They're all from the area
here. So, uh, they were ecstatic about
me coming back and, uh, you know, I
haven't had a chance to really, you miss
a lot of family functions, you know,
when you're away, which is good. My
grandparents are still here. Uh, they're
still alive, so I get a chance to
continue to spend time with them and my
mom and my aunt and uncles. Um, you
know, my wife, she's she's, uh, she
lives in the area, but she's from the
Bay Area, and so she works her her firm
is here located in the Washington DC
area. So, it's always good to just kind
of come back full circle with that. In
terms of the homeless uh question or,
you know, sleeping in a car
again is what you're willing to not what
you're willing to give up, but it's what
you're willing to to do. Um, and so it
was tough, you know, but there was
ultimate goal of uh getting to the
highest level at that particular time.
And you know when you're a young person
and you're single and you're not
married, you have a mindset that uh no
one can outwork you. You don't have any
a wife or a kid to go home to. And so
when I was younger and growing up in the
profession and you know after going
through the challenges and different
things that you've gone through um
you have to pay your dues and that no
one tells you what those dues look like.
Um, but when you're out there and you
want something that you want to
accomplish, what's holding you back? You
got to choose your heart. So, it's
either the hards of failures or the
hards of success. You know, you can be
hard and, you know, I'm sleeping in my
car and it's hard or, you know, I can
have it the easy way, right? And I got
to face the hard of how do I handle
success, you know, if it comes too
early. And so you got to pick your
battles and and and understand that uh
you know you trust in God and you you
pray and he will never lead you
straight. So that's what I did.
>> Appreciate coach.
>> Thank you. Thank you for having me.